jumsoft.com 2018-10-24

# Privacy Policy - Jumsoft

Protecting your privacy is the top priority with everything we do at Jumsoft. All Jumsoft products and services are designed and built in a way to minimize the amount of users’ data they collect. The data that is collected is only used for ensuring the intended quality and functionality of our products and services.

Jumsoft does not collect any information that users store in Jumsoft applications, nor any personally identifiable information related to the downloads, purchases, and/or subscriptions within our applications. All data collected by Jumsoft are anonymous device and account identifiers essential for providing you continuous access to your purchased products and services.

Any data we collect is strictly for improving products, user experience, and ensuring proper functionality of our products. By providing your information you agree to our collection and use of your provided information in accordance with our privacy policy.

Using our products and services results in generating a variety of aggregated non-personally identifiable information, such as device model and software versions, and statistics of purchases or subscriptions. This information is not shared with third parties.

Entering your email address within Jumsoft applications or in appropriate forms in Jumsoft website will be used to provide product and marketing information in the form of newsletters. Every newsletter contains links to unsubscribe. Email addresses are not shared with third parties.

Emailing Jumsoft in form of regular messages or support requests means that your email address will be used to respond to your messages or requests, and to track previous communication with Jumsoft to provide context to any repeated contacts with us. Email addresses and message contents are not shared with third parties.

Opting in to receive notifications within Jumsoft applications provides the device’s Unique Identifier, which is used solely for delivering relevant notifications. This information is not personally identifiable, and is only used to recognize devices that have opted-in for notifications, when the notifications are sent.

Jumsoft website uses cookies to store user’s choices between browsing sessions, including, but not limited to, a choice to receive notifications within the browser from Jumsoft website.

Jumsoft website also uses Google Analytics ([Google Analytics Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)) to better understand users’ behavior in the website to improve and optimize its presentation. The collected information may include: device model, software version, country, pages visited in Jumsoft website. Jumsoft do not share this information with third parties.

By continuing to use Jumsoft products and services you confirm that you have read and agree with this privacy policy.
